<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, JovianSpiral!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Where is Io</string>
    <string name="delete_label">Reset Cache</string>
    <string name="delete_shortcut">D</string>
    <string name="about_label">About...</string>
    <string name="about_shortcut">A</string>
    <string name="about_title">About Where is Io - version 1.1</string>
    <string name="about_text">
Where is Io lets you know where the 4 galliean satellites of Jupiter are
at any given time.  Even through only 8x binoculars you can make out these
4 moons on nights when Jupiter is up.

The portrait view shows a 4 day window of time, with the orange line 
representing the current state.  In landscape view, you get a close up on
the first portion of the graph (total time will vary based on the aspect
ratio of your device).  Jupiter's size is slightly exagerated (2x) for aesthetics.

This is a work in progress, expect to see additional functions rolled out
over time.

Copyright (c) 2010 - Sean Dague (http://dague.net)

This software includes simulation code derived from Johannes Gajdosik\'s vsop87, elp82b, and l1 model
implementations.
Much thanks to his excellent work in porting Fortran models to C and making those available for
general use.

Copyright (c) 2006 Johannes Gajdosik

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a
copy of this software and associated documentation files (the \"Software\"),
to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation
the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense,
and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included
in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_details">\
<b>Radius:</b> 11.209 Earths\n\
<b>Mass:</b> 317.8 Earths\n
\n
Jupiter is the 5th planet from the Sun, and the largest in our solar system.\n
\n\
More info at: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jupiter
</string>
</resources>
